Lore of Attributes


how about: 
	*	attributs dividing points over in attributes to the elements. but thats additional to attributs and changes multipliers?
	*	or attributes just normal?

Attributes serve to calculate how units fare if put to some trial.  Obviously you  want to see the really big numbers here.

attribute::imagination: Imagination describes the influence of one unit onto the world. For example for a mage to successfully weave a spell and thus change the layout of the world, first of all he needs to be able to create an image of the weave in his mind so strong that it becomes real.

attribute::bond: Everybody is bound to the world. However there are some units that are bound so strongly that the world changes to their favor. They can be extremely lucky wherever random factors are involved. You can find those people in underground gambling halls, where they seem to be unbeatable but you might also find some of them inmidst of a battle - where weapons somehow aren't hitting them at all. 