Lore of the Planes

There is an infinite number of planes. This certain plane has always been near to the plane the humans lived in. They gave the plane many different names like Shambhala, Hyperborea, Patala, Mu, Nibiru, Annwn, Asgard, Asphodel Meadows, Shangri-La, Elysian Fields, Lemuria, Themiscyra, Thuvaraiyam Pathi, Atlantis or Utopia, but after they discovered how to travel there, the people who discovered it coined it Eden.
The reason the humans could transfer to Eden is, that Eden is the plane the nearest to the plane of Origin: The Shadow. It's ties to the shadow allowed reflections of Eden to permeate into the mind of the humans. 