Lore of Origin
	Source, Inspiration
	
Age of Empires
The Lord of the Rings
Star Wars
Wheel of Time

Imagine a world, where magic exists. Set in the future, after an apocalypse, after humans had the powers of gods. They warred and destroyed and set up worlds. Some leftovers exist. Guarding the sanctuary worlds created. Against war machines of the old, still roaming the verse.
The world has been created as a reflection of our own. But "magic" exists through old devices, scattered through the world. There are proto romans who could never conquer more than they could stomach, proto egyptians, proto vikings. The world is set in the centuries of the induestrial revolution which does not quite happen, because magic already makes machines kind of obsolete.

Vincentius is set in some irish / english place - ergo where the proto vikings rule or rather raid.