Lore of Anthropology

Anthropology describes the people, places and history of the world.

Taar'Ad
Taar'Ad is a city state in the western end of the big plane. It is known for its cheese and the neverending fight between the two leading classes: The Warriors and Summoners. The cheese is in fact not produced in Taar'Ad itself but rather by the Barul, Nomads living in the plane and trading with Taar'Ad.

Zunft
Zunft is the city of mages. The Zunft collects all magi to gain a monopoly on mana.
